<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PaduaTourGuide</string>
    <string name="padua">Padua</string>
    <string name="padua_arms">padua_arms</string>
    <string name="map">Link to Padua map</string>
    <string name="without">
        Welcome to Padua, the city of the three without.\nThey say in Padua there are a lawn without
        grass, a saint without name and a coffee shop without doors.
    </string>
    <string name="intro_title">A Little Bit of History</string>
    <string name="intro">
        Padua is a city in Northern Italy\’s Veneto region. It\’s known for the frescoes by Giotto in
        its Scrovegni Chapel in 1303–05 and the vast 13th-century Basilica of St. Anthony.
        The basilica, with its Byzantine-style domes and notable artworks, contains the namesake
        saint\’s tomb. In Padua\'s old town are arcaded streets and stylish cafes frequented by
        students of the University of Padua, established in 1222.

        \n\nIn the central area of the Veneto plains, among lagoon, hills and Alpine foothills, lies
        the Province of Padua, a fascinating mixture of art, cultures, flavors and traditions.
        A visit to the Province is a discovery of a territory remarkably rich in history, culture,
        vitality and ingenuity, characterized by a great variety of places to see, products to taste,
        and people to meet. An inventive and hard-working people have known how to renew their
        traditions time and again.

        \n\nIn the Province\'s heart we find Padua, dynamic and vivacious city with a vast historical
        and monumental heritage; it is surrounded by significant natural and cultural attractions:
        the Euganean Springs, the Euganean Hills, the Medieval defensive walls, castles, villas, a
        patchwork countryside and water flows that run east towards the Veneto Lagoon.
        The southeast is occupied by the Euganei Hills, a treasure chest of wonders. Green valleys and
        pretty hills covered in vineyards are made even more beautiful by the colors of spring, and
        the warm atmosphere of autumn.

        \n\nThe hills enclose the largest thermal area in Europe, the Terme Euganei, internationally-renowned
        for their therapeutic waters, that after their long subterranean journey rise to the surface
        here. The principal spa centers are Abano, Montegrotto and Galzigano Terme, and they offer
        mudbath therapies and many of the most modern beauty and wellness treatments.

        \n\nThe Province is also made up of a vast network of navigable waterways. Between Padua and
        Venice, the Brenta River makes a river cruise (Burchiello) an absolutely unforgettable
        experience. Cruisers will feel - even briefly - akin to the lords and aristocrats of
        Venice that used these boats to reach their summer residences - simple buildings that
        they had transformed into magnificent works of architecture, with the help of brilliant
        artists such as Palladio, Preti and Scamozzi.

        \n\nSummertime tours on the canals circling Padua offer unique occasions to see the city from a
        different perspective. Otherwise, experiencing this terrain on a bicycle, exploring the
        network of paths, particularly along rivers and streams, is also an excellent choice: try
        the bike track in Padua or on the Euganean Riviera, or a romantic itinerary on the banks of
        the Battaglia Canal, with its lovely villas and scenic shortcuts through the Hills.

        \n\nA tour of the fortified cities is an intriguing way to get to know Padua\’s long Medieval
        history. Cittadella, Este, Monselice and Montagnana are ideal for living the past, via
        commemorative re-enactments in period costumes, and the palios and jousts that animate these
        ancient villages every year. The area\'s millenary history also shows up in the local arts of
        good cuisine and fine wine. Here, the origins of viticulture are ancient; at the same time,
        cultivation techniques have been perfected over time. The high-quality whites and reds of
        today are the fruits of such meticulous and time-tested labor.

        \n\n(from http://www.italia.it/en/discover-italy/veneto/padua.html)
    </string>

    <!-- Start button -->
    <string name="start_tour">Start Tour</string>

    <!-- Section names -->
    <string name="walking">Walking</string>
    <string name="visit">Visit</string>
    <string name="nearby">Nearby</string>
    <string name="food">Food</string>

    <!-- PLACES -->
    <!-- Place name for walking and visit sections with description -->
    <string name="prato_della_valle">Prato della Valle</string>
    <string name="descr_prato_della_valle">
        The lawn without grass. Prato della Valle is the biggest square in Europe and its
        history is fascinating.
    </string>
    <string name="la_specola">La Specola</string>
    <string name="descr_la_specola">
        This tower is the astronomic observatory where the great Galileo Galilei, professor in Padua
        University, used to study and work.
    </string>
    <string name="pedrocchi">Caffè Pedrocchi</string>
    <string name="descr_cafe_pedrocchi">
        The Caffè without doors. There is a lot of italian history in this caffè designed by
        architect Giuseppe Jappelli in the 18th century.
    </string>
    <string name="salone">Salone della Ragione</string>
    <string name="descr_salone">
        The medieval City Hall. Outside it\'s magnificent, inside it\'s stunning, below it hides a
        wonderful food market.
    </string>
    <string name="piazze">Le Piazze</string>
    <string name="descr_piazze">
        There are three of them, all around the Salone della Ragione.
        Piazza delle Erbe, Piazza della Frutta and Piazza dei Signori, each one with its own market.
    </string>
    <string name="orto_botanico">Orto Botanico</string>
    <string name="descr_orto_boanico">
        It is the world\'s oldest academic botanical garden, founded in 1545.
    </string>
    <string name="teatro_anatomico">Teatro Anatomico</string>
    <string name="descr_teatro_anatomico">
        Padua University is the second most antique university of Italy. This theatre was secretly
        used to study human anatomy since 1594, when this kind of studies were prohibited.
    </string>
    <string name="santo">Basilica del Santo</string>
    <string name="descr_santo">
        The Saint without name. He\'s Sant\'Antonio da Padova, of course, but here we call him and
        his cathedral "Il Santo".
    </string>
    <string name="ghetto">Il Ghetto</string>
    <string name="descr_ghetto">
        From Piazza delle Erbe you can reach the narrow streets of the Ghetto.
    </string>
    <string name="orologio">Torre dell\'Orologio</string>
    <string name="descr_orologio">
        In the beautiful Piazza dei Signori there is the clock tower. Built by Jacopo Dondi
        dell\'Orologio in 1344 it is still working!
    </string>
    <string name="eremitani_musei">Musei Civici Eremitani</string>
    <string name="descr_eremitani">
        An interesting museum full of history and masterpieces. In the adjacent Eremitani\'s church
        you can admire an Andrea Mantegna\'s fresco in the Olivetari Chapel.
    </string>
    <string name="cappella_scrovegni">Cappella degli Scrovegni</string>
    <string name="descr_capella_scrovegni">
        Inside the ancient Roman Arena there is the real jewel of Padua. This Chapel contains a
        fresco cycle by Giotto completed about 1305.
    </string>
    <string name="battistero">Battistero del Duomo</string>
    <string name="descr_battistero">
        This chapel next to the Padua Duomo was completely frescoed by Giusto de Menabuoi about 1375.
    </string>
    <string name="santa_giustina">Basilica di Santa Giustina</string>
    <string name="descr_santa_giustina">
        In Prato della Valle there is the 9th biggest church of the world. You can visit the
        interesting crypt as well as the church.
    </string>
    <!-- Place name for nearby section -->
    <string name="colli">Parco dei Colli Euganei</string>
    <string name="descr_colli">
        A protected area full of nature, traditions, good food and great wine. Take a car and explore it!
    </string>
    <string name="terme">Terme Euganee</string>
    <string name="descr_terme">
        This ancient roman thermal center is still the ideal place to relax in the heart of the
        Parco dei Colli Euganei.
    </string>
    <string name="bike">Bike along the rivers</string>
    <string name="descr_bike">
        If you like bike, discover the hundreds of kilometers of bicycle lanes along the rivers all around
        Padua.
    </string>
    <string name="riviera_brenta">Riviera del Brenta</string>
    <string name="descr_riviera">
        Along the Brenta river, drive from Padua to Venice and discover Antonio Canova\' villas and
        suggestive landscapes.
    </string>
    <string name="burchiello">Il Burchiello</string>
    <string name="descr_burchiello">
        From Padua to Venice by boat, the Burchiello! This historical tour on Brenta river will show
        you Antonio Canova\' villas and suggestive landscapes.
    </string>
    <string name="praglia">Abbazia di Praglia</string>
    <string name="descr_praglia">
        In the heart of the Parco dei Colli Euganei there is this monastery with his abbey which are
        worth a visit.
    </string>
    <string name="cappeller">Parco Cappeller</string>
    <string name="descr_cappeller">
        A rich family decided to help and protect a lot of species and built this educational park.
    </string>
    <string name="monselice">Monselice</string>
    <string name="descr_monselice">
        A nice walk to the villa on the hill passing by seven little churches.
    </string>
    <string name="piazzola">Mercato dell\'Antiquariato</string>
    <string name="descr_piazzola">
        Every last sunday of the month, in front of a beautiful historic villa, you can walk in this
        crazy market full of old stuff.
    </string>

    <!-- FOOD -->
    <!-- Restaurant name and description-->
    <string name="descr_pedrocchi">
        The famous Caffè without doors.\nGo inside and discover why!
    </string>
    <string name="nazionale">Bar Nazionale</string>
    <string name="descr_nazionale">
        This is the best place ever to eat the famous Tramezzino.\nSeat in the beautiful Piazza delle
        Erbe and enjoy your Tramezzino with a Spritz!
    </string>
    <string name="graziati">Graziati</string>
    <string name="descr_graziati">
        A very elegant place for sweets, appetizers and cocktails in the heart of the city..\nTry the
        \"millefoglie\" and you\'ll never forget it!
    </string>
    <string name="orsucci">Orsucci</string>
    <string name="descr_orsucci">
        A unusual Pizza, the most antique and famous of the city, baked in a little pan in the
        wood oven.\nTry one and you\'ll desire to eat all of them!
    </string>
    <string name="paccagnella">Antica Osteria Paccagnella</string>
    <string name="descr_paccagnella">
        A traditional \"osteria\" of Veneto\'s cuisine. Great!
    </string>
    <string name="calandre">Le Calandre</string>
    <string name="descr_calandre">
        One of the most exclusive and expensive restaurant in Italy.\nI never tried it, but critics
        say it\'s truly amazing.
    </string>
    <string name="folperia">La Folperia</string>
    <string name="descr_folperia">
        This is really a stall, but a prize winner one! You can find it in Piazza della Frutta, look
        for a lot of people waiting and you will find it!
    </string>
    <string name="cavour">Caffè Cavour</string>
    <string name="descr_cavour">
        An elegant caffè with delicious tramezzini and a really famous patisserie.
    </string>
    <string name="nane">Trattoria Nane de la Giulia</string>
    <string name="descr_nane">
        A typical hosteria were you can eat home made cuisine and local wine. Here you can hear
        people speaking Padua dialect.
    </string>
    <string name="antico_forno">Antico Forno</string>
    <string name="descr_antico_forno">
        A nice place where you can sit, rest and eat very genuine food and pastry.
    </string>

    <!-- Restaurant address -->
    <string name="dumb_address1">piazza della Frutta, 1</string>
    <string name="dumb_address2">via Roma, 156</string>
    <string name="dumb_address3">Prato della Valle, 86</string>
    <string name="dumb_address4">piazza dei Signori, 73</string>

    <!-- Restaurant telephone -->
    <string name="dumb_phone1">049.6598254</string>
    <string name="dumb_phone2">049.00972489</string>
    <string name="dumb_phone3">049.00972489</string>
    <string name="dumb_phone4">049.88990033</string>

    <!-- Restaurant price -->
    <string name="one_euro">\u20ac</string>
    <string name="two_euros">\u20ac\u20ac</string>
    <string name="three_euros">\u20ac\u20ac\u20ac</string>
    <string name="four_euros">\u20ac\u20ac\u20ac\u20ac</string>

</resources>
